Guide to the Michael J. Bowen sexploitation movie posters, 1959-1974.
Bowen, Michael J. sexplotation movie posters
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Michael J. Bowen sexploitation movie posters, 1959-1974.
7783
Bowen, Michael J.,
109 items.
posters
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Pressbook and single-sheet posters used to advertise pornographic films.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Michael J. Bowen collected sexploitation movie posters for his dissertation on adult film production in New York during the 1960s and 70s in the Department of Cinema Studies at New York University.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Posters, press sheets, and stills used to advertise pornographic films.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Bowen, Michael J.,
Subjects:
Pornographic films -- United States -- Marketing.; Motion pictures -- United States -- Marketing.
Form and Genre Terms:
Posters.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
CONTAINER LIST
- Posters
  - "Price of Flesh", 1959 (Map-case Folder 3)
  - "A Stranger Knocks", 1959, 1969 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "The Seducers", 1962 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "I, a Woman", 1965, 1966 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "The Bed and How to Make It!", 1966 (Map-case Folder 3)
  - "Moonlighting Wives", 1966 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "Yes!", 1968, 1969 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "Scandal in Denmark", 1969 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "Relations", 1969, 1971 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "The Sensual Male", 1970 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "Love Secrets of the Kama Sutra", 1971 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "Together", 1971 (Map-case Folder 3)
  - "Red, White & Blue", 1971 (Map-case Folder 3)
  - "Voices of Desire", 1972 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "Campus Girls" ("The Undergraduate"), 1973 (Map-case Folder 3)
  - "High Rise", 1973 (Map-case Folder 3)
  - "Deep Throat Part II", 1974 (Map-case Folder 3)
  - "Wet Rainbow", 1974 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "The Big Con", 1975 (Map-case Folder 3)
  - "European Lovers", 1975 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "Laura's Toys", 1975 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "Patty", 1976 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "The Honey Cup", 1976 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "Hot Wives", 1977 (Map-case Folder 3)
  - "Sylvia", 1977 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "Tigresses", 1979 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "Deep Inside Annie Sprinkle", 1981 (Map-case Folder 3)
  - "Viva Vanessa", 1984 (Map-case Folder 1)
  - "Little Oral Annie Takes Manhattan", 1985 (Map-case Folder 1)
- Press Sheets (1-sheets)
  - "Carmen Baby", c. 1967 (Map-case Folder 4)
    Radley Metzger
  - "Young Erotic Fanny Hill", 1971 (Map-case Folder 4)
  - "Miss Terri Takes a Liberty", 1973 (Map-case Folder 5)
  - A Touch of Genie, 1974 (Map-case Folder 4)
    New york; Joe Sarno; XXX
  - "Hot Shots" aka "Cheese" (x 2), 1974 (Map-case Folder 5)
  - "Moonshine Girls", 1974 (Map-case Folder 4)
    "lost"
  - "Portrait", 1974 (Map-case Folder 4)
    New York; Gerard Damiano; XXX
  - "Teenage Milkmaid", 1974 (Map-case Folder 4)
    "lost"; New York; XXX
  - They Shall Overcome, 1974 (Map-case Folder 4)
  - "Defiance of Good", 1975 (Map-case Folder 4)
    New York; BDSM; XXX
  - "My Master, My Love", 1975 (Map-case Folder 4)
    New York; BDSM
  - "Sexual Freedom in Brooklyn", 1975 (Map-case Folder 4)
    "lost"; New York
  - "Teenage Sexmaids", 1975 (Map-case Folder 5)
  - "Unwilling Lovers", 1975 (Map-case Folder 6)
  - "The Divine Obsession", 1976 (Map-case Folder 5)
  - "Heavenly Pleasure Girls", 1977 (Map-case Folder 5)
  - "My Sex-Rated Wife", 1977 (Map-case Folder 5)
  - "Trouble with Young Stuff", 1977 (Map-case Folder 6)
    Joe Sarno; New York; XXX
  - "For Richer, For Poorer", 1979 (Map-case Folder 6)
    New York; Gerard Damiano
  - "Deep Rub", 1979 (Map-case Folder 6)
    BDSM; XXX
  - "Deviates in Love", 1979 (Map-case Folder 6)
  - "Best of the New York Erotic Film Festival", mid-1970s (Map-case Folder 6)
    In German
  - "Executive Secretary", mid-1970s (Map-case Folder 6)
  - "The Love Cycle", 1970s (Map-case Folder 6)
    "lost"; XXX
- Stills
  - "Flesh & Lace" 8 x 10, 1965 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - "The Love Merchant" 8 x 10, 1965 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - "Sexperts: Touched by Temptation" 8 x 10, 1965 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - "Bad Girls Go To Hell" 8 x 10, 1965 (Map-case Folder 2)
- Pressbooks
  - "The Flamboyant Sex", 1962 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - "Sexus", 1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    sexploitation; import
  - "Sylvia's Girls", 1965 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - "Caught in the Act", 1966 (Map-case Folder 2)
    lost, sexploitation
  - "Honey" (x 2), 1966 (Map-case Folder 2)
    Unfolded
    "lost"; sexploitation
  - "Twisted Sex", 1966 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - "Come Ride the Wild Pink Horse" (x 2), 1967 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - "My Body Hungers", 1967 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - "Spree", 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    "lost"; Jane Mansfield; sexploitation
  - "Commuter Game", 1969 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - "Meeting on 69th Street", 1969 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - "Gathering of Evil", 1969 (Map-case Folder 5)
  - "Eve and the Mermaid", mid 1960s (Map-case Folder 2)
    Unfolded.
    "lost"; nudist exploitation
  - "The Whistleblowers", 1973 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - "Not Just Another Woman", 1974 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - "Sweet & Sour", 1974 (Map-case Folder 2)
  - "The Affairs of Janice", 1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    New York; XXX
  - "Chickie", mid-1970s (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - "Christy", mid-1970s (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - "Descendance of Grace", mid-1970s (Box 1, Folder 6)
    "lost";New York; XXX
  - "Heat Wave", mid-1970s (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Lobby Cards
  - "Lady Chatterly's Lover", 1957 (Map-case Folder 5)
    Pre-sexploitation import
  - "The Seduction of Inga", 1971 (Map-case Folder 5)
    Soft-core
- Records (sound recordings)
  - "Hard Women", 1970; SR-6322 (Box 1)
  - "Main Street Woman", c. 1970; SR-6323 (Box 1)
  - "The Naughty Cheerleader", 1970; SR-6324 (Box 1)
  - "Angels' Wild Women", 1972; SR-6325 (Box 1)
  - "The Lonely Woman", 1973; SR-6326 (Box 1)
  - "The Naughty Stewardess", 1975; SR-6327 (Box 1)